- 3000, for the sake of
everybody in the band,
act like you've got some sense.
- He ain't goin' go up
there and shake his ass.
- Were we talkin' to you?
Go get out there playin' the (beep), okay?
- We 'id that every night,
that's all I know how
to do, man, you know?
- I ain't flew overseas in the middle seat
for us to get over here and (beep) up,
act like you got some sense.
You might get a little bit of this here.
Not (beep) money, this is hope money.
I hope you get out
there and do your thing.
Hey, check it out. Hey, hey.
You know what I'm saying?
- All right.
- You think you can follow that?
3000, I'm telling you. Don't
mess it up for everybody.
Greyhound don't float on water.
- Here in London for the first time
to perform for you live
Johnny Vulture, Benjamin
Andre, Dookie on drums,
Possum Jenkins, and Andre Ice Cold 3000
performing their smash hit "Hey Ya,"
ladies and gents, I give
you the love, the love.
(audience cheers)
- One, two, three, uh!
♪ My baby don't mess around ♪
♪ Because she loves me so ♪
♪ And this I know fo sho ♪
♪ But does she really wanna ♪
♪ But can't stand to see
me walk out the door ♪
♪ Don't try to fight the feeling ♪
♪ Because the thought alone
is killin' me right now ♪
♪ Thank God for Mom and Dad ♪
♪ For sticking two together ♪
♪ 'Cause we don't know how ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Hey ya ♪
♪ You think you've got it ♪
♪ Oh, you think you've got it ♪
♪ But got it just don't get it
'til there's nothin' at all ♪
♪ We get together ♪
♪ Oh, we get together ♪
♪ But separate's always better ♪
♪ When there's feelings involved ♪
♪ If what they say is ♪
♪ "Nothing is forever" ♪
♪ Then what makes, then what makes ♪
♪ Love the exception ♪
♪ So why, oh, why, oh ♪
♪ Why, oh, why, oh, why, oh ♪
♪ Are we so in denial when we
know we're not happy here ♪
♪ Y'all don't want to hear
me, you just want to dance ♪
♪ Hey ya ♪
♪ Uh oh ♪
♪ Don't want to meet your daddy ♪
♪ Just want you in my Caddy ♪
♪ Uh oh ♪
♪ Don't want to meet your mama ♪
♪ Hey ya ♪
♪ Uh oh ♪
♪ Just want to make you ♪
♪ I'm, I'm, I'm just being honest ♪
♪ I'm just being honest ♪
♪ Hey, alright now ♪
♪ Alright now, fellas ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Now, what cooler than being cool ♪
♪ Ice cold ♪
♪ I can't hear you ♪
♪ I say what's, what's
cooler than being cool ♪
♪ Ice cold ♪
♪ Alright, alright,
alright, alright, alright ♪
♪ Alright, alright, alright, alright ♪
♪ Okay, now ladies ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Now, we gon' break this thang
down in just a few seconds ♪
♪ Now, don't have me break
this thang down for nothin' ♪
♪ Now, I want to see y'all
on y'all baddest behavior ♪
♪ Lend me some sugar, I am your neighbor ♪
♪ Ah, here we go ♪
♪ Shake it, shake, shake it,
shake it, shake, shake it ♪
♪ Shake it, shake, shake
it, shake it, shake it ♪
♪ Shake it like a
Polaroid picture, hey ya ♪
♪ Shake it, shake, shake it,
shake it, shake, shake it ♪
♪ Shake it, shake it, shake it, sugar ♪
♪ Shake it like a Polaroid picture ♪
♪ Now, all Beyonce's, and Lucy Liu's ♪
♪ And baby dolls, get on the floor ♪
♪ Get on the floor, you know what to do ♪
♪ You know what to do ♪
♪ Hey ya ♪
♪ Uh oh ♪